[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gary Wallace", "correct_answer": "Weird Science", "incorrect_answers": ["Nate and Hayes", "Some Kind of Wonderful", "Shes Having a Baby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After week 27 you can do the following experiment: switch on a flashlight against your belly and the baby will move towards the light.   What allows this to happen?", "correct_answer": "it opens its eyes", "incorrect_answers": ["its head can move", "its hearing started functioning", "its brain started growing quickly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1999 movie Cleopatra starred Timothy Dalton, Billy Zane and Elizabeth Taylor.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The echidnas diet consists mainly of this group of animals.", "correct_answer": "Insects", "incorrect_answers": ["Mammals", "Fish", "Birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed James Bond in the 1971 movie Diamonds Are Forever?", "correct_answer": "Sean Connery", "incorrect_answers": ["George Lazenby", "Roger Moore", "Timothy Dalton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular movie villain uttered the words A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice Chianti?", "correct_answer": "Hannibal Lecter", "incorrect_answers": ["Nurse Ratched", "Cruella de Vil", "Dracula"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Stegosaurus had no teeth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In one of the freecreditreport.com commercials, the singers relegated to riding a bicycle for transportation. How is the singer rolling in this ad?", "correct_answer": "eco-friendly", "incorrect_answers": ["loaded", "life friendly", "phat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Neptune has rings around it just like Saturn.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Disney movie is this quote taken from: My little babys all grown up and...*sniff* ... and savin China. You have a tissue?", "correct_answer": "Mulan", "incorrect_answers": ["Who Framed Roger Rabbit", "The Emperors New Groove", "The Sword in the Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What property of microfiber makes it ideal for the making of clothes and underwear?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Absorbency", "Heat retention", "Elasticity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The African vampiric creature, known as Adze, was believed to take the form of this animal in order to hunt children.", "correct_answer": "Firefly", "incorrect_answers": ["Lizard", "Snake", "Bat"]}]